I think that people like me who have good taste.
People who are "white collared"
It's natural we should drive nice cars.
That's why Honda is my favorite brand.
When you drive a nice car, it's like you're flying.
So when I drive my Honda, I feel like the whole world is flying.
When I'm driving, people are envious of me.
Only people who drive Hondas can have this feeling.
One day, I was passed by a red QQ car.
I thought "How dare this QQ driver try pass a Honda".
This guy was looking for trouble.
Not only should you not disrespect a Honda, you should never disrespect someone who's  white collared.
I easily just stepped on the gas and forced the QQ off the road.
QQ's are such terrible cars. Without even saying a word, I vandalized the QQ.
The QQ driver was furious, but I calmly said:
Driving a QQ wasn't your mistake. Your mistake was trying to challenge a Honda.
You can't possible match up to a Honda.
Take me for example. Someone with so much taste.
An ideal white collared person.
And then look at my car. So valuable. So luxurious.
Because you dared pass me, you deserve to have your car vandalized.
All the people who were watching began applauding.
I left to a rousing ovation.